

CONTACT

C

+33 6 14 07 15 21



Ile de France, France



/Guillaume-93



/guillaume-brechaire



g.brechaire@gmail.com

QUALITIES

- Autonomy
- Curiosity
- Organization
- Rigor
- Logical mind

SKILLS



Javascript



React.js



Html 5



Git / GitHub



CSS 3



SQL / PostgreSQL



SASS



Typescript



Node.js / Express



Tailwind

INTERESTS

- Science
- Astronomy
- Manga
- Series
- Search for knowledge

GUILLAUME BRÉCHAIRE

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

After more than fourteen years of experience in the field of weak currents, I chose to reorient myself towards web development, attracted by new technologies and digital innovation. Graduated in Web and Mobile Web Development (DWWM), I am passionate about solving technical problems and paying attention to detail. Specialized in React, I also master backend development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

World Wide Wins

February 2024 to May 2024

- Participation in the development of a showcase site for a client.
- Collaboration with the development team to improve the user experience.
- Used Next.js and Tailwind for front-end development.

WEB AND MOBILE WEB DEVELOPER

O'clock School - End of training project January 2024 to February 2024



- Creation of a web application as a team, from its design to the deployment of an MVP using agile methodology.
- Creation of the front-end of the "<u>Atlas of the Forgotten Kingdoms</u>" site in total autonomy. Using React, Redux and Tailwind CSS to develop a responsive and modern user interface

LOW CURRENT TROUBLESHOOTER

IECF PESIER - September 2009 to April 2023

- Diagnose and resolve technical problems related to low current systems. Site
 creation on Visiosoft web, Résidorg. Programming of proximity and HF
 badges.
- Perform installations, configurations and upgrades of communications and security systems.
- Perform preventive and corrective maintenance on manufacturers' equipment.
- Follow up on troubleshooting requests, respecting deadlines and providing quality customer service.
- Collaborate closely with internal teams to ensure customer satisfaction and effective problem resolution.
- Train customers in the use of systems and provide technical support.

TRAINING

RNCP Level 5 title 'Web and Mobile Web Developer'

Sept 2023 - Feb 2024

O'Clock School - Fullstack Javascript Web Developer Training Promo: Gyoza

- 3 months of basic: HTML / CSS / Javascript
- 1 month of Front-end specialization: React.js
- 1 month of professional group project

BEP Electronic

Sept 2003 - June 2005

Lycée Polyvalent Louis Armand - Electrical and electronic engineering